ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Photo of Unity House, Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 2)
  formerly bx 75 (wrapped)
- Entrance to Forest Park Hotel, Forest park, PA, Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 3)
  formerly bx 74 (wrapped)
- Photos of Triangle Fire mounted on backer board, Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 4)
  formerly bx 78 (wrapped)
- The Worthless Fire Escape and the Death Trap Below it (Triangle Fire Photos), Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 5)
  formerly bx 79 (wrapped)
- Would it not be better to mar the architectural beauty of the City with a few fire escapes? (Triangle Fire), Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 6)
  formerly bx 80 (wrapped)
- Forest Park Hotel - Forest Park, PA, Black and white photograph (Box 120, Folder 7)
  formerly bx 73 (wrapped)
- Oversize Photo - formerly in a photo album housed in box 122 (folders 3-6), 1946; Black and white photograph (Box 121, Folder 1)
  March 26, 1946 - Induction of former New York State Governor Charles Poletti as Impartial Chairman of Coat & Suit Industry
- David Dubinsky photograph, Black and white photograph (Box 121, Folder 2)
  formerly in box 71
- N.V.V. Women's Camps - Photo album, Black and white photograph (Box 121, Folder 3)
- 40th Anniversary Convention - ILGWU - May 27-June 7, 1940 - New York City, Black and white photograph (Box 121, Folder 4)
  1 panoramic photo now housed in 2 OP, and 3 panoramic now housed in Mapcase 20 - this photo album formerly housed in box 72 - 43 photos
- ILGWU Dubinsky Hospital in Beer Sheba Israel, Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 1)
  Photo album formerly housed in box 71 -- 7 photographs
- Golden Door Award to David Dubinsky: Presented by American Council for Nationalities Service, 1965; Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 2)
  Photo album formerly housed in box 71 - 33 photographs
- Unlabeled Photo Album (Pt.1) 1929-1946, Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 3)
  too large to fit in one folder -- formerly housed in box 71 -- 26 photos
- Unlabeled Photo Album (pt.2): 1941-1945, Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 4)
  too large to fit in one folder -- formerly housed in box 71 -- 26 photographs
- Unlabeled Photo Album: (pt. 3) 1946-1948, Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 5)
  too large to fit in one folder - formerly housed in box 71 -- 27 photographs
- Unlabeled Photo Album - (pt.4) 1948-1959, Black and white photograph (Box 122, Folder 6)
  too large to fit in one folder -- formerly housed in box 71 -- 21 photographs
- 5 Panoramic Photos, 1940-1950; Black and white photograph (Box 123, Folder 1)
  Convention Hall, Atlantic City, NJ - May 23-June 1; Convention Hall, May 23rd-June 1st, 1950, Atlantic City, N.J.; ILGWU Convention at World's Fair, New York, June 2, 1940; Delegates to the 24th Convention, 40th Anniversary, ILGWU, New York City, May 27-June 8, 1940; Vacation Center of the ILGWU, Unity House, Forest Park, PA, 1940
- Panoramic photo, formerly in photo album from box 72, 1940; Black and white photograph (Box 124, Folder 1)
  ILGWU Convention at World's Fair, New York - June 2, 1940
- David Dubinsky Scrapbook, Black and white photograph; News clipping; Text (Box 124, Folder 1)
- Images digitized from the collection., Black and white photograph; News clipping; Text (Box 125)